<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guffey on Guffeyville</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/guffey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guffey on Guffeyville</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/guffey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eleven Mile Reservoir, Spinney Reservoir, and the Dream Stream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/eleven-mile-reservoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/eleven-mile-reservoir/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling the Fishing Paradise: The Dream Stream, Eleven Mile Reservoir, and Spinney Reservoir A Fisherman’s Dream Near Guffey, Colorado Welcome to the angler&amp;rsquo;s dreamland just outside the charming town of Guffey, Colorado! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned fisherman or a casual enthusiast, this area offers a bounty of fishing opportunities. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the wonders of the renowned Dream Stream, Eleven Mile Reservoir, and Spinney Reservoir, all conveniently close to our cozy lodge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Restauraunts Near Paradise Cove, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/best_restauraunts_near_paradise_cove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/best_restauraunts_near_paradise_cove/</guid>
      <description>Discover the Charm of Paradise Cove and Wild Spirit Mountain Lodge Paradise Cove (Guffey Gorge) Paradise Cove, also known as Guffey Gorge, is a hidden gem nestled in the Rocky Mountains near Guffey, Colorado. This natural swimming hole is a favorite spot for locals and visitors seeking adventure and relaxation. The gorge features crystal-clear waters surrounded by dramatic cliffs, making it a picturesque destination for swimming, cliff jumping, and picnicking. The hike to Paradise Cove is relatively short but offers stunning views of the surrounding wilderness, providing a perfect blend of tranquility and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of Guffey, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/guffey-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/guffey-history/</guid>
      <description>The History of Guffey, Colorado Early Beginnings Nestled in the Rocky Mountains, Guffey, Colorado, has a rich history that dates back to the late 1800s. Founded as a mining town during Colorado&amp;rsquo;s gold rush, Guffey quickly became a bustling hub for prospectors and settlers looking to make their fortune. The discovery of gold, silver, copper, and other minerals in the area brought an influx of people, transforming the once-quiet region into a lively community.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
