<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Guffey, Colorado</title>
    <link>http://localhost:59871/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Guffey, Colorado</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:59871/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eleven Mile Reservoir, Spinney Reservoir, and the Dream Stream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/eleven-mile-reservoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/eleven-mile-reservoir/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling the Fishing Paradise: The Dream Stream, Eleven Mile Reservoir, and Spinney Reservoir A Fisherman’s Dream Near Guffey, Colorado Welcome to the angler&amp;rsquo;s dreamland just outside the charming town of Guffey, Colorado! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned fisherman or a casual enthusiast, this area offers a bounty of fishing opportunities. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the wonders of the renowned Dream Stream, Eleven Mile Reservoir, and Spinney Reservoir, all conveniently close to our cozy lodge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guffey Farmer&#39;s Markets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/guffey-farmers-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/guffey-farmers-markets/</guid>
      <description>The New Guffey Farmers&amp;rsquo; Market Every Saturday | 9 AM - 12 PM | July 13th - October 5th Located at the Guffey Bakery &amp;amp; Bistro, the Guffey Farmers&amp;rsquo; Market is a fresh addition to our community events, starting this year. Held every Saturday morning from mid-July to early October, the market is a lively celebration of local agriculture, crafts, and services.&#xA;Support and Access The market aims to support youth, veterans, and rural trades, providing a platform for local producers and artisans from Park, Teller, and Fremont Counties to showcase their offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Bars in Guffey, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/best-bar-in-guffey-colorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/best-bar-in-guffey-colorado/</guid>
      <description>Best Bars in Guffey, Colorado Nestled in the picturesque Rocky Mountains, Guffey, Colorado, may be small, but it offers a unique charm with its cozy bars and welcoming atmosphere. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a local or just passing through, these bars are sure to provide a memorable experience.&#xA;1. Wild Spirit Mountain Lodge Located at 1245 Canon Street, Wild Spirit Mountain Lodge is more than just a bar&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s a community hub. Known for its rustic charm, this venue offers a cozy bar with a selection of drinks that cater to all tastes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Restauraunts Near Paradise Cove, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/best_restauraunts_near_paradise_cove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/best_restauraunts_near_paradise_cove/</guid>
      <description>Discover the Charm of Paradise Cove and Wild Spirit Mountain Lodge Paradise Cove (Guffey Gorge) Paradise Cove, also known as Guffey Gorge, is a hidden gem nestled in the Rocky Mountains near Guffey, Colorado. This natural swimming hole is a favorite spot for locals and visitors seeking adventure and relaxation. The gorge features crystal-clear waters surrounded by dramatic cliffs, making it a picturesque destination for swimming, cliff jumping, and picnicking. The hike to Paradise Cove is relatively short but offers stunning views of the surrounding wilderness, providing a perfect blend of tranquility and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antique Store in Guffey, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/antique-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/antique-store/</guid>
      <description>The Antique Store in Guffey, Colorado Nestled in the charming town of Guffey, Colorado, the local Antique Store is a treasure trove waiting to be explored. This quaint shop offers a unique blend of history and nostalgia, featuring a wide array of vintage items, collectibles, and rare finds. Whether you’re an avid collector or just love browsing through pieces of the past, the Antique Store in Guffey promises a delightful experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is Guffey Colorado?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/where-is-guffey-colorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/where-is-guffey-colorado/</guid>
      <description>Where is Guffey, Colorado? Guffey, Colorado, is a small, historic town located in the heart of the Rocky Mountains, within Park County. Nestled at an elevation of approximately 8,700 feet, Guffey is surrounded by stunning natural landscapes, including the Pike National Forest and the Royal Gorge. The town is situated about 50 miles southwest of Colorado Springs and 40 miles west of Cañon City.&#xA;Getting to Guffey From Denver: Take US-285 S for about 86 miles, until about 1 mile past Fairplay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of Guffey, Colorado</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59871/post/guffey-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59871/post/guffey-history/</guid>
      <description>The History of Guffey, Colorado Early Beginnings Nestled in the Rocky Mountains, Guffey, Colorado, has a rich history that dates back to the late 1800s. Founded as a mining town during Colorado&amp;rsquo;s gold rush, Guffey quickly became a bustling hub for prospectors and settlers looking to make their fortune. The discovery of gold, silver, copper, and other minerals in the area brought an influx of people, transforming the once-quiet region into a lively community.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
